Let's go over the Rainbow Chest Move.
This movement will combine both the Torso Slide and the Chest Lift.
Make sure your feet are parallel, your knees are slightly bent, your belly button's pulled in towards your spine, your chest is lifted, shoulders are relaxed and down.
Arms are out to the side.
Let's begin by first sliding the chest to the side.
Go to your full range of motion.
Now we're going to lift the chest and then bring it across to the other side and letting it release.
Let's go back the other direction, up and over.
So that way you think about having a nice little rainbow.
So again go from side to side.
Be sure to keep your belly button engage to your spine and not arching your back.
Let's try it with some music.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Let's try doing that in the mirror at home.